<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="horoscope_names">
        <item>Aries</item>
        <item>Taurus</item>
        <item>Gemini</item>
        <item>Cancer</item>
        <item>Leo</item>
        <item>Virgo</item>
        <item>Libra</item>
        <item>Scorpio</item>
        <item>Sagittarius</item>
        <item>Capricorn</item>
        <item>Aquarius</item>
        <item>Pisces</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="reminder_options">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Amrit</item>
        <item>Chal</item>
        <item>Kaal</item>
        <item>Labh</item>
        <item>Rog</item>
        <item>Shubh</item>
        <item>Udweg</item>
    </array>
    <array name="reminder_values">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Amrit</item>
        <item>Chal</item>
        <item>Kaal</item>
        <item>Labh</item>
        <item>Rog</item>
        <item>Shubh</item>
        <item>Udweg</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="months_array">
        <item>January</item>
        <item>February</item>
        <item>March</item>
        <item>April</item>
        <item>May</item>
        <item>June</item>
        <item>July</item>
        <item>August</item>
        <item>September</item>
        <item>October</item>
        <item>November</item>
        <item>December</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- Face Locations -->
    <string-array name="face_locations">
        <item>Forehead</item>
        <item>Cheek</item>
        <item>Nose</item>
        <item>Chin</item>
        <item>Eyebrow</item>
        <item>Ear</item>
        <item>Lip</item>
        <item>Jawline</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Body Locations -->
    <string-array name="body_locations">
        <item>Arm</item>
        <item>Leg</item>
        <item>Back</item>
        <item>Chest</item>
        <item>Stomach</item>
        <item>Shoulder</item>
        <item>Hip</item>
        <item>Hand</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_forehead">
    <item>A mole on the {location} signifies leadership and authority. It suggests that you have a natural ability to take charge and inspire others.
    </item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} indicates intelligence and analytical skills. It suggests that you are logical and capable of finding practical solutions to problems.
    </item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests creativity and a visionary outlook. It indicates that you have innovative ideas and a unique perspective on life.
    </item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a strong sense of independence and self-reliance. It suggesst that you value freedom and autonomy in your decisions.
    </item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a charismatic personality and influence over others. It indicates that you have a magnetic presence and can captivate people.
    </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_cheek">
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies charm and grace. It suggests that you have a warm and friendly personality that attracts others.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} indicates a nurturing and caring nature. It suggests that you are compassionate and empathetic towards others.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a creative and artistic flair. It indicates that you have a talent for expressing yourself through art or creativity.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies good health and vitality. It suggests that you have a strong immune system and physical resilience.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a social and outgoing personality. It indicates that you enjoy connecting with people and making new friends.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_nose">
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies strong intuition and keen insight. It suggests that you have a deep understanding of people and situations.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} indicates a love for adventure and new experiences. It suggests that you enjoy exploring different cultures and places.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a romantic and passionate nature. It indicates that you are deeply connected to your emotions and relationships.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies financial success and wealth. It suggests that you will experience prosperity and abundance in your career and investments.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a strong willpower and determination. It indicates that you can overcome challenges with resilience and perseverance.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_chin">
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies determination and persistence. It suggests that you are focused on achieving your goals and overcoming obstacles.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} indicates practicality and reliability. It suggests that you are dependable and capable in handling responsibilities.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a strong sense of family and loyalty. It indicates that you value relationships and prioritize the well-being of loved ones.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a strong sense of justice and fairness. It suggests that you advocate for equality and stand up for what is right.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a dynamic and adventurous spirit. It indicates that you enjoy exploring new opportunities and taking risks.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_eyebrow">
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a creative mind and a knack for problem-solving. It indicates that you can think outside the box and find innovative solutions.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a strong sense of identity and self-expression. It suggests that you are confident in who you are and how you present yourself.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} indicates a sharp intellect and quick thinking. It suggests that you can process information rapidly and make decisions with clarity.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a bold and adventurous spirit. It indicates that you are not afraid to take risks and explore new opportunities.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a deep connection to your intuition and instincts. It suggests that you trust your gut feelings and follow your inner guidance.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_ear">
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a good listener and empathetic nature. It indicates that you are attentive to others\' needs and supportive in your relationships.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a curious and open-minded personality. It suggests that you enjoy learning new things and exploring different perspectives.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a harmonious and balanced temperament. It indicates that you strive for peace and seek harmony in your interactions.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a strong sense of intuition and inner wisdom. It suggests that you trust your instincts and are guided by inner knowledge.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a love for music and the arts. It indicates that you appreciate beauty and are sensitive to the emotional power of creativity.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_lip">
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a passionate and expressive nature. It indicates that you communicate with emotion and intensity, making your words impactful.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a romantic and affectionate personality. It suggests that you value intimate connections and enjoy expressing love.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests charisma and charm. It indicates that you have a magnetic presence and can captivate others with your personality.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies creativity and artistic talent. It suggests that you have a flair for drama and enjoy expressing yourself through various forms of art.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a sensitive and intuitive nature. It indicates that you are attuned to the emotions of others and can empathize deeply.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_jawline">
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies resilience and strength. It suggests that you have the ability to overcome challenges and bounce back from adversity.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} indicates determination and perseverance. It suggests that you are steadfast in pursuing your goals and achieving success.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a practical and pragmatic approach to life. It indicates that you make decisions based on logic and reason.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a strong sense of identity and self-assurance. It suggests that you are confident in who you are and what you stand for.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a protective and nurturing personality. It indicates that you are caring and supportive towards your loved ones.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_arm">
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies strength and resilience. It suggests that you have the endurance to overcome challenges and achieve your goals.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} indicates a proactive and action-oriented approach. It suggests that you take initiative and are not afraid to pursue your ambitions.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a dynamic and adventurous spirit. It indicates that you enjoy exploring new opportunities and taking risks.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a strong work ethic and dedication. It suggests that you are committed to your responsibilities and strive for excellence.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests independence and self-reliance. It indicates that you value freedom and prefer to make your own decisions.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_leg">
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a love for travel and exploration. It suggests that you enjoy discovering new cultures and experiencing different lifestyles.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} indicates a strong sense of adventure and curiosity. It suggests that you are open to new experiences and eager to learn.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a free-spirited and spontaneous personality. It indicates that you embrace change and adapt easily to new environments.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies stamina and endurance. It suggests that you have the physical resilience to handle challenges and maintain your energy levels.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a philosophical and reflective nature. It indicates that you ponder life\'s deeper questions and seek meaning in your experiences.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_back">
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a supportive and protective nature. It indicates that you are there for others in times of need and offer comfort and reassurance.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies resilience and inner strength. It suggests that you have the ability to overcome adversity and bounce back from challenges.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a cautious and observant personality. It indicates that you are attentive to details and prefer to assess situations carefully.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a compassionate and empathetic nature. It suggests that you understand the emotions of others and offer support without judgment.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a harmonious and balanced temperament. It indicates that you seek peace and strive to maintain a calm and stable environment.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_chest">
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a nurturing and caring nature. It suggests that you prioritize the well-being of others and create a supportive environment.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} indicates a strong emotional connection to loved ones. It suggests that you value relationships and cherish moments of intimacy.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a sensitive and intuitive personality. It indicates that you are attuned to the feelings of others and respond with empathy.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a creative and imaginative mind. It suggests that you have a unique perspective and enjoy exploring new ideas.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a generous and giving spirit. It indicates that you derive satisfaction from helping others and making a positive impact.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_stomach">
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a strong intuition and gut instinct. It indicates that you trust your instincts and rely on inner guidance in decision-making.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies stability and security. It suggests that you prioritize comfort and seek a stable foundation in your personal and professional life.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a practical and methodical approach. It indicates that you prefer to plan ahead and make decisions based on logic.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a nurturing and supportive nature. It suggests that you care deeply for others and strive to create a harmonious environment.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a strong connection to family and home. It indicates that you value traditions and prioritize the well-being of loved ones.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_shoulder">
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies responsibility and leadership. It suggests that you take charge in situations and are trusted to make decisions.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} indicates a strong sense of duty and commitment. It suggests that you fulfill your responsibilities diligently and prioritize obligations.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a supportive and protective nature. It indicates that you are there for others and offer guidance and assistance.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies resilience and determination. It suggests that you persevere through challenges and achieve your goals with persistence.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a caring and compassionate personality. It indicates that you empathize with others\' struggles and provide comfort and support.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_hip">
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a desire for freedom and independence. It indicates that you value autonomy and prefer to make your own decisions.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a fun-loving and adventurous spirit. It suggests that you enjoy exploring new experiences and seeking thrills.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a strong sense of identity and self-expression. It indicates that you are confident in who you are and embrace your individuality.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a generous and compassionate nature. It suggests that you care deeply for others and offer support without expecting anything in return.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a curious and inquisitive mind. It indicates that you enjoy learning and discovering new things about the world around you.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mole_interpretations_hand">
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a practical and resourceful nature. It suggests that you find solutions to problems and adapt to changing circumstances.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} indicates a proactive and action-oriented approach. It suggests that you take initiative and are not afraid to pursue your goals.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a creative and artistic talent. It indicates that you have a knack for expressing yourself through various forms of art.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} signifies a strong work ethic and dedication. It suggests that you are committed to achieving excellence in your endeavors.</item>
        <item>A mole on the {location} suggests a strategic and analytical mind. It indicates that you think critically and make decisions based on logic and reason.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>